(Howard:)Those are business expenses.
(Howard:)You can write those off.
A $200 R2-D2 is
a business expense?
(Howard:)Oh, Bernie,
(Howard:)you're gonna have to sound
a lot more confident
(Howard:)when we get audited.
(cell phone rings)
(Howard:)Hey, what's up?
Eh, Emily ran back
to the hospital,
(Raj:)so I'm just hanging out
at her place.
(Raj:)What are you, uh,
what are you doing?
(Howard:)Just playing video games
while Bernie does the taxes.
(Raj:)What are you, a little kid?
(Raj:)Is she gonna cut your dinner
into little pieces, too?
(Howard:)She doesn't have to--
I filled up on jelly beans.
(Raj:)So, uh, what game are you...
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Emily:)Crap.
(Howard:)What's wrong?
I can't get Emily's
nightstand to close.
(Howard:)So?
She's gonna know
I was looking in it.
(Howard:)Why were you looking in it?
(Raj:)Well, there's a question
(Raj:)I better have a good answer to
before she gets back.